And I thought I'd just show you a couple ideas that I have in there.
For one, it's got a lot of gels, transparent gels that I have painted on top of the wax and they come in art stores different--there's transparent, then there's marbled effects on the different gels and I've used that, painted it on top of the wax and on some cases there, I've actually dusted that when it was wet with some metallic powders just to get some different looks.
So, this is one thing that's in there.
Another thing that is kind of interesting is that I took a DVD like this.
I took an embossing gun and I heated the DVD and once you heat that DVD, you can then take a pair of scissors and actually cut that DVD up like that.
So, once you have a piece of that DVD cut out, you could then take a rubber stamp.
And you could stamp an image on that DVD like this.
Now, there's an image of this half face on that DVD.
I could cut that out more so as a square like it's shown on that painting up there.
And then on top of that, I could take some heavy embossing powder and I could melt it in a melting pot like this here.
And once it was all melted, I could take the melted fluid and pour it on top of the DVD to create a totally different effect on top and then I set that into the painting.
So, that's just one of the many effects on this painting that I thought I would talk to you about.